{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042713678","data":{"timestamp":" 947042713678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042714063","data":{"timestamp":" 947042714063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042714558","data":{"timestamp":" 947042714557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042714912","data":{"timestamp":" 947042714912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042715327","data":{"timestamp":" 947042715326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042715812","data":{"timestamp":" 947042715811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042716043","data":{"timestamp":" 947042716042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042719277","data":{"timestamp":" 947042719277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042719317","data":{"timestamp":" 947042719317"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042720046","data":{"timestamp":" 947042720045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042720451","data":{"timestamp":" 947042720450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042720752","data":{"timestamp":" 947042720752"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042720968","data":{"timestamp":" 947042720968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042721175","data":{"timestamp":" 947042721175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042721502","data":{"timestamp":" 947042721502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042721742","data":{"timestamp":" 947042721741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042724922","data":{"timestamp":" 947042724921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042725334","data":{"timestamp":" 947042725333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042727939","data":{"timestamp":" 947042727938"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042728152","data":{"timestamp":" 947042728152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042728362","data":{"timestamp":" 947042728361"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042731906","data":{"timestamp":" 947042731905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042735661","data":{"timestamp":" 947042735660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042736697","data":{"timestamp":" 947042736696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042739417","data":{"timestamp":" 947042739416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042739805","data":{"timestamp":" 947042739804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042740298","data":{"timestamp":" 947042740298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042740658","data":{"timestamp":" 947042740657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042741073","data":{"timestamp":" 947042741072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042741559","data":{"timestamp":" 947042741559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042741794","data":{"timestamp":" 947042741794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042745046","data":{"timestamp":" 947042745045"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042745084","data":{"timestamp":" 947042745084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042745813","data":{"timestamp":" 947042745812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042746220","data":{"timestamp":" 947042746219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042746530","data":{"timestamp":" 947042746530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042746745","data":{"timestamp":" 947042746745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042746951","data":{"timestamp":" 947042746950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042747279","data":{"timestamp":" 947042747278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042747515","data":{"timestamp":" 947042747514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042750088","data":{"timestamp":" 947042750087"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042750201","data":{"timestamp":" 947042750201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 9a6a942d-6543-4c45-b277-e8fcfea60e3f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042783066","data":{"timestamp":" 947042783065"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042785529","data":{"timestamp":" 947042785529"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042787134","data":{"timestamp":" 947042787133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042790933","data":{"timestamp":" 947042790933"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042792543","data":{"timestamp":" 947042792542"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042795740","data":{"timestamp":" 947042795740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042797343","data":{"timestamp":" 947042797342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042800460","data":{"timestamp":" 947042800459"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042802077","data":{"timestamp":" 947042802076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042804577","data":{"timestamp":" 947042804576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042806179","data":{"timestamp":" 947042806179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042808811","data":{"timestamp":" 947042808810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042810432","data":{"timestamp":" 947042810431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UDONGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042813257","data":{"timestamp":" 947042813256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UDONGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042814856","data":{"timestamp":" 947042814855"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042817415","data":{"timestamp":" 947042817415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042819440","data":{"timestamp":" 947042819439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042819584","data":{"timestamp":" 947042819584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" f8adee34-5e99-488c-adcd-f522a23dc2c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042835372","data":{"timestamp":" 947042835371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" UZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042843878","data":{"timestamp":" 947042843878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042845500","data":{"timestamp":" 947042845500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042848351","data":{"timestamp":" 947042848350"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UYOGA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UYOGA"," userResponse":" UYOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042849957","data":{"timestamp":" 947042849957"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042852554","data":{"timestamp":" 947042852554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKUTA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKUTA"," userResponse":" UKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042854163","data":{"timestamp":" 947042854162"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042857327","data":{"timestamp":" 947042857326"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UKULIMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKULIMA"," userResponse":" UKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042858948","data":{"timestamp":" 947042858947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042861455","data":{"timestamp":" 947042861455"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UBAO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UBAO"," userResponse":" UBAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042863052","data":{"timestamp":" 947042863051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042865291","data":{"timestamp":" 947042865291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UA"," userResponse":" UA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042866916","data":{"timestamp":" 947042866916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UDONGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042869491","data":{"timestamp":" 947042869490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UDONGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDONGO"," userResponse":" UDONGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042871102","data":{"timestamp":" 947042871101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042876470","data":{"timestamp":" 947042876470"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-U.rand.35__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042878509","data":{"timestamp":" 947042878507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042878645","data":{"timestamp":" 947042878644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" a323a828-169f-4344-a0e9-089ff039eddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-U.rand.35__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" UGALI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042905667","data":{"timestamp":" 947042905667"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" cbf9ae87-a5d4-4338-af67-24150ecff02c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-E-U"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042910488","data":{"timestamp":" 947042910488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" cbf9ae87-a5d4-4338-af67-24150ecff02c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-L-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042914083","data":{"timestamp":" 947042914083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" cbf9ae87-a5d4-4338-af67-24150ecff02c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_E-U-P"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042917466","data":{"timestamp":" 947042917465"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" cbf9ae87-a5d4-4338-af67-24150ecff02c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_P-H-U"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042928653","data":{"timestamp":" 947042928652"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" cbf9ae87-a5d4-4338-af67-24150ecff02c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_P-M-U"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042934676","data":{"timestamp":" 947042934676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" cbf9ae87-a5d4-4338-af67-24150ecff02c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-H-S"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042938425","data":{"timestamp":" 947042938424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" cbf9ae87-a5d4-4338-af67-24150ecff02c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_K-U-D"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042941681","data":{"timestamp":" 947042941680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" cbf9ae87-a5d4-4338-af67-24150ecff02c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_A-U-S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042945421","data":{"timestamp":" 947042945420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" cbf9ae87-a5d4-4338-af67-24150ecff02c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-V-A"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042951792","data":{"timestamp":" 947042951792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" cbf9ae87-a5d4-4338-af67-24150ecff02c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947042957560","data":{"timestamp":" 947042957559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" cbf9ae87-a5d4-4338-af67-24150ecff02c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043029183","data":{"timestamp":" 947043029182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" cbf9ae87-a5d4-4338-af67-24150ecff02c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_U..U.all.rand.all.stat.show.65"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_U_F-U-S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043077974","data":{"timestamp":" 947043077974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" e1213ed0-f473-4935-a963-e3a0725d3a9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_E_U"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043084649","data":{"timestamp":" 947043084649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" e1213ed0-f473-4935-a963-e3a0725d3a9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_P_V"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043091309","data":{"timestamp":" 947043091308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" e1213ed0-f473-4935-a963-e3a0725d3a9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_M_Y"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043097939","data":{"timestamp":" 947043097939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" e1213ed0-f473-4935-a963-e3a0725d3a9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_V_Y"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043104640","data":{"timestamp":" 947043104640"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" e1213ed0-f473-4935-a963-e3a0725d3a9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_W_K"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043111287","data":{"timestamp":" 947043111287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" e1213ed0-f473-4935-a963-e3a0725d3a9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_V_N"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043117941","data":{"timestamp":" 947043117940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" e1213ed0-f473-4935-a963-e3a0725d3a9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_P_U_B"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043124547","data":{"timestamp":" 947043124547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" e1213ed0-f473-4935-a963-e3a0725d3a9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_Y_V"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043131165","data":{"timestamp":" 947043131165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" e1213ed0-f473-4935-a963-e3a0725d3a9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_K_U_Y"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043137816","data":{"timestamp":" 947043137816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" e1213ed0-f473-4935-a963-e3a0725d3a9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_V_U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:U..U.all.10.rand.say.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043149871","data":{"timestamp":" 947043149870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" e1213ed0-f473-4935-a963-e3a0725d3a9e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_U..U.all.10.rand.say.34"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_M_V_U"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043174119","data":{"timestamp":" 947043174119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 1f2b3ab8-8938-48cf-b24d-fbffd0f34c1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043174272","data":{"timestamp":" 947043174272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 1f2b3ab8-8938-48cf-b24d-fbffd0f34c1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043174368","data":{"timestamp":" 947043174367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 1f2b3ab8-8938-48cf-b24d-fbffd0f34c1b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043192712","data":{"timestamp":" 947043192712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_062445"," gameId":" 241f2296-92af-403c-b459-45d82eda5eb2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}